solrepublic.com 2015-11-08

# Privacy Policy | SOL REPUBLIC

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to SOLREPUBLIC.com. As a visitor to SOL REPUBLIC, your trust is our most important asset. We take the protection and proper use of your personal information seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information in our possession. In order to preserve your trust, we want you to understand what personally identifiable or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our website, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.

**SOL REPUBLIC.com Privacy Policy**

In this policy, the words "we", "our", and "us" refer to SOL REPUBLIC and the phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state, zip), e-mail address, telephone number, etc.

**Categories of Personally Identifiable Information We Collect**  
We collect personally identifiable information, as defined above, from you when you register for an account, purchase product on our website, request that merchandise be sent to you or others, request an e-receipt, subscribe to SOLREPUBLIC.com E-mail Updates, through communications with you, or through SOL REPUBLIC. We may also collect personal information about you from other third parties, such as demographic firms, to make our future service and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your personal information that we collect to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products, services and experience. Service providers, third parties who perform services on our behalf, are contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us to provide you with the products and services available from SOL REPUBLIC. We may also, in certain instances, disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, or bring legal action to protect your rights or the rights of SOL REPUBLIC or others. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required by law.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Our website uses "cookie" and "web beacon" technology. We use cookies and web beacons to distinguish you from other visitors, track your IP address and usage of our site, and to identify the name of the Web site from which you linked to SOL REPUBLIC.com. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. Non-personally identifiable information obtained through cookies and web beacons may be shared with or obtained by service providers on our behalf. More information is available under Third-Party Advertising Partners.

A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. A web beacon is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie.

When you visit our website, we may use both a session and a persistent cookie. This SOL REPUBLIC-placed cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track your usage of our website and in some cases, your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is only saved in this SOL REPUBLIC-placed cookie if you register with us. A web beacon allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a web site, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed, and details about any items that were purchased.

If you register with us, this SOL REPUBLIC-placed cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information or order from us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. If you have not saved your information or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. You can disable cookies at any time by using your browser options; however, if you turn off cookies, we will not be able to track your order or enable you to make a purchase from our website. In addition, we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information.

**Third-Party Advertising Partners**  
We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf across the Internet.

These service providers may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products. Such non-personally identifiable information is anonymous and does not include your name, address, e-mail address or other personal information. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag (also known as cookies and action tags), which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites.

In addition to the anonymous information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the anonymous information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products available from SOL REPUBLIC as well as future events and additional material or enhancements made to our website.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third-party service providers, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Links to Other Websites and Services**  
Websites provided by SOL REPUBLIC may include links to other Internet sites maintained by third parties ('Linked Sites'). SOL REPUBLIC provides Linked Sites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of Linked Sites does not imply endorsement by SOL REPUBLIC of the Linked Sites. You access Linked Sites at your own risk and by accessing them you leave SOL REPUBLIC's website. Linked Sites are not under the control of SOL REPUBLIC and SOL REPUBLIC is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site.

**Your Information, Your Choice**  
To update us with your information-sharing preferences, you may contact us using one of the following methods:

• [support@SOLREPUBLIC.com](mailto:support@solrepublic.com?subject=Customer%20Support%20Inquiry)  
• SOLREPUBLIC.com/general-contact

Please note your preference as stated below:

• "I prefer not to receive e-mail advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events." (You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all SOL REPUBLIC.com e-mail advertisements to be removed from future e-mail updates.)

• "I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events." (Please note that direct mail requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective.)

**Children's Privacy**  
SOL REPUBLIC will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person less than 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent.

If we become aware that an individual is less than the age of 13 and has submitted any information to SOL REPUBLIC for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files.

**Security**  
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personally identifiable information transmitted to us using this website. To guard your information, our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only SOL REPUBLIC is able to decode your information. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

To be sure your connection is secure, look at the bottom status bar of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser) the SSL is active and your information is secure. Most browsers offer additional security alerts as well. If for some reason you are unable to connect to our secure server, please contact us at [support (at) SOLREPUBLIC.com](mailto:support@solrepublic.com?subject=).

**International Customer Privacy**  
The privacy and protection of information about our SOL REPUBLIC customers is a top priority. In some cases, SOL REPUBLIC partners with outside vendors to help facilitate transactions. When that is the case, we work closely with the vendor to ensure that the transaction is appropriately handled and all the information you provide is treated with the utmost care.

To sell and fulfill online purchases that customers choose to ship internationally, SOL REPUBLIC contracts with companies that will carefully process your personal information, with at least the same level of privacy protection set forth in the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles as established by the U.S. Department of Commerce and approved by the European Commission. Any partnering vendor also agrees not to sell, transfer, or otherwise use your information other than for executing international shipping orders. On the Checkout page you will be required to submit credit card and personal information (name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address and phone number) to complete your order. Once you place your order, you will be prompted to confirm whether you would like to receive future marketing communication from SOL REPUBLIC.

If you choose to provide SOL REPUBLIC with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. SOL REPUBLIC adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles as established by the U.S. Department of Commerce and approved by the European Commission. We conduct periodic self-assessments to verify that we are in compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles in addition to our own SOL REPUBLIC privacy program assessments. SOL REPUBLIC has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union that our processing of personal data is in compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles.

Customers shipping internationally who wish to inquire about or update personal information or change marketing preferences, or anyone who wants to receive information about our international privacy program should contact us directly using one of the following methods:

• [support@SOLREPUBLIC.com](mailto:support@solrepublic.com?subject=Customer%20Support%20Inquiry)  
• [SOLREPUBLIC.com/general-contact](https://solrepublicstaging-my.bislr.com/website/editor/page_E85871CF-A7DE-423E-8F90-2580554A7611#)

In order to comply with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, SOL REPUBLIC commits to resolve any inquiries or complaints for all international shoppers including European Union citizens relating to privacy and our collection or use of personal information. Any complaints which cannot be resolved directly with SOL REPUBLIC will be resolved through the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.'s Safe Harbor Privacy Dispute Resolution Procedures.

Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.  
BBB EU Safe Harbor  
4200 Wilson Boulevard, Suite 800  
Arlington, VA 22203  
Phone: 703-276-0100  
Web: [www.us.bbb.org](http://www.us.bbb.org/)  
E-mail: [eusafeharbor@council.bbb.org](mailto:eusafeharbor@council.bbb.org)

**Business Transitions**

As we continue to develop our business, we may undergo a business transition such as acquiring another company, merging with an existing company, or selling a portion of our assets. In such transitions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. In the unlikely event that SOL REPUBLIC, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired or enter a court proceeding, you acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that your Personal Information can continue to be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Policy Changes**  
This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our website.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**  
You may come in contact with websites, e-mails or texts that try to lure you into providing personal information with the offer of a SOL REPUBLIC gift card. SOL REPUBLIC does not sponsor these offers nor are we affiliated with the promotion originators. If you become aware of any potentially fraudulent activity on a website or in an e-mail or text, please forward the information to [support@SOLREPUBLIC.com](mailto:support@SOLREPUBLIC.com) so that we can follow up. We take these matters, and the protection of our customers' sensitive information, very seriously.

**Additional Information**  
If you're not comfortable shopping online (and would prefer to make your purchase via telephone), please feel free to buy products through our retail partners.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at:  
• [support@SOLREPUBLIC.com](mailto:support@solrepublic.com?subject=Customer%20Support%20Inquiry)  
• [SOLREPUBLIC.com/general-contact](https://solrepublicstaging-my.bislr.com/website/editor/page_E85871CF-A7DE-423E-8F90-2580554A7611#)

The examples contained in this Privacy Policy are illustrations only, and are not intended to be exhaustive.
